No one can stand before God’s throne
By keeping rules or deeds we’ve shown
God’s holy word reveals our blame
No work we do can cleanse our shame
We all have failed and gone astray
We all fall short of God’s glory and way
By grace alone, through faith we’re saved
In Christ our hope, no more enslaved
It was His blood, God’s wrath appeased
The price He paid, our souls released
By grace alone, this we believe
Upon the cross, God’s wrath was poured
Its burning force Christ bravely bore
He drank the cup that we deserved
Soaked up the fury our sins had earned
The cross displayed what justice cost
Yet grace is free to those who're lost
By grace alone, through faith we’re saved
In Christ our hope, no more enslaved
It was His blood, God’s wrath appeased
The price He paid, our souls released
By grace alone, this we believe
My sin, my debt, His gift, His grace
Christ shed His blood, He took my place
His life, His death, His work complete
There at the cross justice and mercy meet
By grace alone, through faith we’re saved
In Christ our hope, no more enslaved
It was His blood, God’s wrath appeased
The price He paid, our souls released
By grace alone
Through faith alone
In Christ alone
That's how we are saved